<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mother Care</string>
    <string name="login_to_existing_account">Login to Existing Account</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="send_password_reset_email">Send Password Reset Email</string>
    <string name="Title">Save Your Woman</string>
    <string name="find_doctor">Find Doctor</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="places_api_key">AIzaSyA0dX5H7KFB0e_tPlRT3ODaBufEYhUDYSs</string>

    <string-array name="interval">
        <item>Once</item>
        <item>Daily</item>
        <item>Weekly</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard">DashboardActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="home_second">Home Second</string>


    <string name="next">NEXT</string>

    <string name="details">Please Enter Your Details</string>

    <string name="requried">Required fields are marked with*</string>

    <string name="fname">First Name*</string>

    <string name="lname">Last Name*</string>


    <string name="province">Province*</string>

    <string name="city">City*</string>

    <string name="area">Area*</string>

    <string name="address">Street Address*</string>

    <string name="mobile">Mobile Number*</string>

    <string name="phone">Phone Number</string>


    -
    <string-array name="province">

        <item>SINDH</item>

        <item>PUNJAB</item>

        <item>BALOCHISTAN</item>

        <item>K.P</item>

        <item>FEDERAL</item>

    </string-array>


    -
    <string-array name="area">

        <item>Banaras Coloney</item>

        <item>DHA Karachi</item>

        <item>North Karachi</item>

        <item>Sea Side</item>

        <item>Layari</item>

    </string-array>


    <string name="jsonArray"></string>

    <string name="whatis">A pregnancy lasts for about 40 weeks. The weeks are grouped into three trimesters. The first trimester is the time in between fertilization of the egg by the sperm (conception) and week 12 of a pregnancy. A woman’s body goes through many changes during the first 12 weeks of a pregnancy. Women often start to have concerns over: "\n""\n" • What to eat"\n" • Which types of prenatal tests they should consider"\n" • How much weight they might gain"\n" • How they can make sure their baby stays healthy"\n""\n"Understanding a pregnancy week by week can help you make informed decisions and prepare for the big changes that lie ahead. </string>

    <string name="ftbodychanges">In the first trimester, a woman’s body goes through many changes. The body releases hormones that affect almost every single organ in the body. The first sign you may be pregnant is missing a period. As the first few weeks pass, some women experience the following:"\n""\n" • Tiredness"\n" • Upset stomach"\n" • Throwing up"\n" • Mood swings"\n" • Tender breasts"\n" • Heartburn"\n" • Weight gain"\n" • Headaches"\n" • Cravings for certain foods"\n" • Revulsion to certain foods"\n" • Constipation"\n""\n"You may need to rest more or eat smaller meals during this time. Some women, however, don’t feel any of these symptoms at all."\n" </string>

    <string name="the_first_day_of_your_pregnancy_is_also_the_first_day_of_your_last_menstrual_period_at_about_10_to_14_days_after_an_egg_is_released_combines_with_a_sperm_and_conception_occurs">The first day of your pregnancy is also the first day of your last menstrual period. At about 10 to 14 days after, an egg is released, combines with a sperm, and conception occurs.</string>

    <string name="about_a_week_after_conception_between_days_seven_and_10_the_fertilized_ovum_attaches_to_the_lining_of_the_uterus_and_the_placenta_starts_to_form_by_about_two_weeks_when_you_miss_your_first_period_the_embryo_becomes_a_layered_disc_on_the_uterine_wall_as_shown_below_by_about_four_weeks_major_body_systems_are_starting_to_develop">About a week after conception, between days seven and 10, the fertilized ovum attaches to the lining of the uterus and the placenta starts to form. By about two weeks, when you miss your first period, the embryo becomes a layered disc on the uterine wall. As shown below, by about four weeks, major body systems are starting to develop</string>

    <string name="tooth_buds_are_present_fingernails_and_toenails_are_forming_immature_kidneys_secrete_urine_to_the_bladder_external_genitalia_are_forming_the_fetus_can_now_move_in_the_amniotic_fluid_but_you_can_t_feel_it_your_healthcare_provider_may_be_able_to_hear_the_fetal_heart_rate_with_an_electronic_listening_device">Tooth buds are present. Fingernails and toenails are forming. Immature kidneys secrete urine to the bladder. External genitalia are forming. The fetus can now move in the amniotic fluid, but you can’t feel it. Your healthcare provider may be able to hear the fetal heart rate with an electronic listening device.</string>

    <string name="the_first_three_months_of_pregnancy_the_first_trimester_is_a_critical_time_your_baby_is_growing_and_developing_rapidly_and_is_most_at_risk_from_hazards_such_as_smoking_alcohol_drugs_infections_and_x_rays_by_the_end_of_the_first_trimester_all_your_baby_s_organs_will_be_formed_and_functioning">The first three months of pregnancy – the first trimester - is a critical time. Your baby is growing and developing rapidly, and is most at risk from hazards such as smoking, alcohol, drugs, infections and X rays. By the end of the first trimester, all your baby’s organs will be formed and functioning.</string>

    <string name="ftdoctorconsultation"> When you first learn you are pregnant"\n""\n" 1. Make an appointment with your doctor to begin caring for the developing baby."\n" 2. If you are not already on prenatal vitamins, start them immediately."\n" 3. Ideally, women take folic acid (in prenatal vitamins) for a year before the pregnancy."\n" 4. Women normally see their doctor once a month during the first trimester."\n""\n" During your first visit, a doctor will take a full health history and perform a full physical and pelvic exam. The doctor may also:"\n""\n" • perform an Ultrasound to confirm the pregnancy"\n" • perform a Pap test"\n" • take your blood pressure"\n" • test for sexually transmitted infections, HIV, and hepatitis"\n" • estimate your date of delivery or “due date,” which is around 266 days from the first day of your last period"\n" • screen for risk factors like anemia"\n" • check thyroid levels"\n" • check your weight"\n""\n" At around 11 weeks"\n" The doctor will perform a test called a nuchal translucency (NT) scan. The test uses an ultrasound to measure the baby’s head and thickness of the baby’s neck. The measurements can help determine the chance that your baby will be born with a genetic disorder known as Down syndrome."\n""\n" Ask your doctor whether or not genetic screening is recommended for your pregnancy. Genetic screening is a test used to find out your baby’s risk for specific genetic diseases."\n" </string>

    <string name="it_s_important_for_a_woman_to_be_aware_of_what_to_do_and_what_to_avoid_while_pregnant_in_order_to_take_care_of_themselves_and_their_developing_baby">It’s important for a woman to be aware of what to do and what to avoid while pregnant in order to take care of themselves and their developing baby.</string>

    <string name="ftwhattodo">Here are good personal health measures to take during the first trimester:"\n" • Take prenatal vitamins."\n" • Exercise regularly."\n" • Work out your pelvic floor by doing Kegel exercises."\n" • Eat a diet high in fruits, vegetables, low-fat forms of protein, and fiber."\n" • Drink lots of water."\n" • Eat enough calories (about 300 calories more than normal)."\n" </string>

    <string name="ftwhattoavoid">These things should be avoided during the first trimester:"\n" • strenuous exercise or strength training that could cause an injury to your stomach"\n" • alcohol"\n" • caffeine (no more than one cup of coffee or tea per day)"\n" • smoking"\n" • illegal drugs"\n" • raw fish or smoked seafood (no sushi)"\n" • shark, swordfish, mackerel, or white snapper fish (they have high levels of mercury)"\n" • raw sprouts"\n" • cat litter, which can carry a parasitic disease called toxoplasmosis"\n" • unpasteurized milk or other dairy products"\n" • deli meats or hot dogs"\n" </string>

    <string name="ftwhatelsetoavoid">Body changes provide plenty to think about during the first trimester, but having a baby will affect other parts of your life too. There are many things to start to think about during the first few months of your pregnancy so you can prepare for the future. </string>

    <string name="ftifyouhaveahighriskpregnancy">High-risk pregnancy means that there is a greater chance of complications. Factors that may make your pregnancy high-risk include:"\n" • being young"\n" • being over 35 years old"\n" • being overweight"\n" • being underweight"\n" • having high blood pressure, diabetes, HIV, cancer or other autoimmune disorders"\n" • being pregnant with twins or multiples"\n" Women with a high-risk pregnancy may need to visit the doctor more often and sometimes may need a specially trained doctor. Having a high-risk pregnancy doesn’t necessarily mean you will have any problems."\n" </string>

    <string name="stwhatis">A pregnancy lasts for about 40 weeks. The weeks are grouped into three trimesters. The second trimester includes weeks 13 through 27 of a pregnancy."\n""\n"In the second trimester, the baby grows larger and stronger and many women begin showing a larger belly. Most women find that the second trimester is a lot easier than the first, but it’s still important to be informed about your pregnancy during the second trimester. Understanding your pregnancy week by week can help you make informed decisions and prepare for the big changes ahead. </string>

    <string name="stbodychanges">During the second trimester of pregnancy, symptoms that you may have experienced during the first trimester begin to improve. Many women report that nausea and fatigue begin to lessen and they consider the second trimester the easiest and most enjoyable part of their pregnancy. The following changes and symptoms may occur:"\n" • the uterus expands"\n" • you begin to show a larger abdomen"\n" • dizziness or lightheadedness due to lower blood pressure"\n" • feeling the baby move"\n" • body aches"\n" • increased appetite"\n" • stretch marks on the stomach, breast, thighs, or buttocks"\n" • skin changes, like darkening of the skin around your nipples, or patches of darker skin"\n" • itching"\n" • swelling of the ankles or hands"\n""\n" Call your doctor if you experience any of these symptoms:"\n" • nausea"\n" • vomiting"\n" • jaundice (yellowing of the whites of the eyes)"\n" • extreme swelling"\n" • rapid weight gain"\n" </string>

    <string name="stfetusdevelopment">The baby’s organs become fully developed during the second trimester. The baby can also start to hear and swallow. Small hairs become noticeable. Later on in the second trimester, the baby will begin to move around. It will develop sleeping and waking cycles that a pregnant woman will begin to notice."\n""\n" According to the American Pregnancy Association, by the end of the second trimester the baby will be around 14 inches in length and weigh a little over two pounds. </string>

    <string name="_20_weeks_eyebrows_and_eyelashes_appear_a_fine_downy_hair_lanugo_appears_all_over_the_baby_s_body_and_may_be_present_at_birth_the_skin_is_thin_shiny_and_covered_with_a_creamy_protective_coating_called_vernix_oil_glands_appear_the_baby_s_legs_lengthen_and_move_well_teeth_develop_enamel_and_dentine_are_being_formed_this_can_begin_as_early_as_14_weeks_by_the_end_of_the_fifth_month_baby_is_about_half_the_length_of_a_newborn_meconium_baby_s_first_poop_begins_to_appear_in_the_intestines">20 weeks: Eyebrows and eyelashes appear. A fine downy hair (lanugo) appears all over the baby’s body and may be present at birth. The skin is thin, shiny and covered with a creamy protective coating called vernix. Oil glands appear. The baby’s legs lengthen and move well. Teeth develop – enamel and dentine are being formed (this can begin as early as 14 weeks). By the end of the fifth month, baby is about half the length of a newborn. Meconium (baby’s first poop) begins to appear in the intestines.</string>

    <string name="stdoctorconsultation">Women should see a doctor about every two to four weeks during the second trimester of pregnancy. Tests that the doctor may perform during a visit include:"\n""\n" • Measuring your blood pressure"\n" • Checking your weight"\n" • Ultrasound"\n" • Diabetes screening with blood tests"\n" • Birth defect and other genetic screening tests"\n" • Amniocentesis"\n""\n" During the second trimester, your doctor can use an ultrasound test to determine whether or not your baby is a boy or a girl. Deciding whether or not you want to know the sex of the baby before you give birth is your own choice."\n" </string>

    <string name="stwhattodo"> • Continue to take prenatal vitamins."\n" • Exercise regularly."\n" • Work out your pelvic floor by doing Kegel exercises."\n" • Eat a diet high in fruits, vegetables, low-fat forms of protein, and fiber."\n" • Drink lots of water."\n" • Eat enough calories (about 300 calories more than normal)."\n" • Keep your teeth and gums healthy. Poor dental hygiene is linked to premature labor."\n" </string>

    <string name="stwhattoavoid"> • strenuous exercise or strength training that could cause an injury to your stomach "\n" • alcohol"\n" • caffeine (no more than one cup of coffee or tea per day)"\n" • smoking"\n" • illegal drugs"\n" • raw fish or smoked seafood"\n" • shark, swordfish, mackerel, or white snapper fish (they have high levels of mercury)"\n" • raw sprouts"\n" • cat litter, which can carry a parasite that causes toxoplasmosis"\n" • unpasteurized milk or other dairy products"\n" • deli meats or hot dogs"\n" • the following prescription drugs: isotretinoin (Accutane) for acne, acitretin (Soriatane) for psoriasis, thalidomide (Thalomid), and ACE inhibitors for high blood pressure"\n""\n" Ask your doctor if you have any concerns about the prescription drugs or supplements you are taking."\n" </string>

    <string name="stprepareforbirth"> Although there are still several weeks left in the pregnancy, you may want to plan for delivery earlier to help make the third trimester less stressful. Here are some things you can do now to prepare for birth:"\n" "\n" • Take prenatal education classes that are offered locally."\n" • Consider classes on breastfeeding, infant CPR, first aid, and parenting."\n" • Educate yourself with online research."\n" • Watch birth videos on YouTube that are natural and not frightening."\n" • Tour the hospital or birth center where you will be giving birth."\n" • Make a nursery or space in your house or apartment for the newborn baby."\n""\n" Consider whether or not you want to take medication for the pain during delivery."\n" </string>

    <string name="ttwhatis">A pregnancy lasts for about 40 weeks. The weeks are grouped into three trimesters. The third trimester includes weeks 28 through 40 of a pregnancy."\n""\n"The third trimester can be both physically and emotionally challenging for a pregnant woman. The baby is considered full term at the end of week 37 and it’s only a matter of time before the baby will be born. Researching and understanding what to expect during the third trimester can help reduce any anxiety you may have during the final stages of your pregnancy. </string>

    <string name="ttbodychanges"> In the third trimester a woman may experience more aches, pain, and swelling as she carries around her baby. A pregnant woman may also begin to become anxious about her delivery."\n""\n"Other events that occur during the third trimester include:"\n" • A lot of movement by the baby"\n" • Occasional random tightening of the uterus"\n" • Going to the bathroom more often"\n" • Heartburn"\n" • Swollen ankles, fingers, or face"\n" • Hemorrhoids"\n" • Difficulty sleeping"\n""\n"Call your doctor immediately if you experience:"\n" • Painful contractions of increasing intensity"\n" • Bleeding at any time"\n" • Sudden decrease in activity by your baby"\n" • Extreme swelling"\n" • Rapid weight gain"\n" </string>

    <string name="ttdoctorconsultation">1. You will meet with your doctor more regularly during the third trimester. Around week 36, your doctor may perform a Group B strep test to test for a bacterium that can be very harmful to a baby."\n" 2. Your doctor will give you antibiotics if you test positive."\n" 3. Your doctor will check you progress with a vaginal exam. Your cervix will become thinner and softer as you near your due date in order to help the birth canal open during the birthing process."\n" </string>

    <string name="ttstayhealthy">It’s important to be aware of what to do and what to avoid as your pregnancy continues in order to take care of yourself and your developing baby.</string>

    <string name="ttwhattodo"> • Continue to take prenatal vitamins."\n" • Stay active unless you’re experiencing swelling or pain."\n" • Work out your pelvic floor by doing Kegel exercises."\n" • Eat a diet high in fruits, vegetables, low-fat forms of protein, and fiber."\n" • Drink lots of water."\n" • Eat more than 300 calories than normal day."\n" • Stay active with walking."\n" • Keep your teeth and gums healthy."\n" • Get plenty of rest and sleep."\n" </string>

    <string name="ttwhattoavoid"> • Strenuous exercise or strength training that could cause an injury to your stomach"\n" • Alcohol"\n" • Caffeine (no more than one cup of coffee or tea per day)"\n" • Smoking"\n" • Illegal drugs"\n" • Raw fish or smoked seafood"\n" • Shark, swordfish, mackerel, or white snapper fish (they have high levels of mercury)"\n" • Raw sprouts"\n" • Cat litter, which can carry a parasite that causes toxoplasmosis"\n" • Unpasteurized milk or other dairy products"\n" • Deli meats or hot dogs"\n" • The following prescription drugs: isotretinoin (Accutane) for acne, acitretin (Soriatane) for psoriasis, thalidomide (Thalomid), and ACE inhibitors for high blood pressure"\n" • Long car trips and airplane flights, if possible (after 34 weeks, airlines may not let you board the plane because of the possibility of an unexpected delivery on the plane)"\n""\n"If you must travel, stretch your legs and walk around at least every hour or two. </string>

    <string name="ttprepareforbirth">If you haven’t done this already, make a decision on where you plan to give birth to your child. These last-minute preparations can help make delivery go more smoothly:"\n""\n" • Attend a prenatal class if you haven’t already. This is an opportunity to learn about what to expect during labor and the different options available for delivery."\n" • Find a family member or friend who can care for your pets or other children."\n" • Cook some meals that can be frozen and eaten after you get home with the baby."\n" • Have an overnight bag packed and ready with items for you and your baby."\n" • Plan the route and mode of transportation for getting to the hospital."\n" • Have a car seat set up in your vehicle."\n" • Develop a birth plan with your doctor. This may include deciding who you want in your labor room for support, concerns you have about hospital procedures, and pre-registering with your insurance information."\n" • Arrange maternity leave with your employer."\n" • Have a crib ready for your baby and double-check that it’s up to date and safe."\n" • If you receive any “hand-me-down” equipment like cribs, and strollers, make sure they conform to current government safety standards. Purchase a new car seat."\n" • Check that your smoke detectors and carbon monoxide detectors in your home are working properly."\n" • Have emergency numbers, including poison control, written somewhere close to your phone."\n" • Stock up on baby supplies, like diapers, wipes, and baby clothing in different sizes."\n" • Celebrate your pregnancy with friends and family."\n" </string>

    <string name="labour_exp">Every woman’s experience of labour is different. But there are several signs that labour may be starting. You may experience:"\n""\n" 1.a ‘show’, which is when the mucus plug from your cervix comes away – it appears as a pink-brown jelly-like blob or in pieces"\n" 2.pains in your tummy that may feel like strong period pains – these these are the start of contractions"\n" 3.lower back pain"\n" 4.an urge to go to the toilet – this is caused by your baby’s head pressing on your bowel."\n" 5.Your waters may also break or you might start feeling contractions."\n" </string>

    <string name="call_your_midwife_birth_centre_or_hospital_labour_ward_and_tell_them_what_s_happening_the_start_of_labour_is_called_the_latent_stage_and_can_last_hours_or_for_some_women_days_if_you_are_more_than_37_weeks_with_an_uncomplicated_pregnancy_you_ll_probably_be_advised_to_stay_at_home_until_your_labour_is_established_this_is_when_your_cervix_opens_dilates_to_at_least_4cm_and_your_contractions_become_stronger_and_more_regular">Call your midwife, birth centre or hospital labour ward and tell them what’s happening. The start of labour is called the latent stage and can last hours or, for some women, days. If you are more than 37 weeks with an uncomplicated pregnancy, you’ll probably be advised to stay at home until your labour is ‘established’. This is when your cervix opens (dilates) to at least 4cm and your contractions become stronger and more regular.</string>

    <string name="once_labour_gets_going_your_contractions_will_become_more_regular_and_won_t_go_away_call_your_midwife_birth_centre_or_hospital_labour_ward_when_you_are_having_a_contraction_every_5_minutes_that_last_30_60_seconds_if_you_have_chosen_a_home_birth_the_midwife_will_come_to_you_if_this_is_not_your_first_baby_or_you_are_likely_to_have_a_quick_labour_your_midwife_may_advise_you_to_call_earlier_than_this">Once labour gets going, your contractions will become more regular and won\'t go away. Call your midwife, birth centre or hospital labour ward when you are having a contraction every 5 minutes that last 30–60 seconds. If you have chosen a home birth, the midwife will come to you.If this is not your first baby, or you are likely to have a quick labour, your midwife may advise you to call earlier than this.</string>

    <string name="call_the_labour_ward_or_your_midwife_if_you_re_still_not_sure_whether_you_re_in_labour_they_are_used_to_dealing_with_false_alerts_so_don_t_worry_about_wasting_anyone_s_time">Call the labour ward or your midwife If you\'re still not sure whether you\'re in labour.They are used to dealing with false alerts so don\'t worry about wasting anyone’s time.</string>
</resources>
